

Daniel **O**jo



SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Profile

My name is Ojo Daniel a IT expert having the knowledge of software design with modern development techniques and technologies. I am able to work effectively as a team member and efficiently manage one's own time when working on independent projects.

Contact



+234 8151314563



danielbankole33@yahoo.com



https://ojodanieltechguy.github.io/ OjoDanielPortfolio/



Surulere, Lagos Nigeria.

Education

(2018 - 2020)

YABA COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY

National Diploma in Computer Science **Upper Credit**

Experiences

Oct 2022 - Feb 2023

GRANDIDA LLC

Solidity Developer

- Developing and deploying smart contracts
- Testing on the Ethereum network
- Testing business logic
- Developing application based on Ethereum

(2021 - September 2022)

FAVOUR KONSULT LTD

IT Expert / Consultant

- Developing business models
- Negotiate contract terms with clients
- Develop and maintain client relationship
- Scheduling and coordinating meetings



Task

Managemnet

Familiarity with **Blockchain Tools** **Skills**

Team Leadership

Verbal and written communication skills

Problemsolving skills

